# 广东 佛山 拍摄于1月初
Foshan, Guangdong, video shot in early January
# 他来了 他来了
Here he comes, here he comes
# 他带着我们的牛杂来了
Comes with our beef offal!
# 看我后面 就是我们今天要去的牛杂小吃摊
Look what's behind me. This is the beef offal shop that we plan to try today
# 走吧
Let's go
# 凳子当桌子
Chairs used as tables
# 我以为自己来得很早
I thought that I came here very early
# 但是比我早来的人还真不少
But there are quite a few people who came even earlier than me
# 在这排着队
Lining up here
# 能闻着五香牛杂的香气
You can smell the aroma of the beef offal
# 大哥 这一锅都是一样的价格吗
Bro, do they share the same price?
# 啊
Yes?
# 我说不同部位的肉都是一样价吗
I mean, does the meat from different parts have the same price?
# 是一样的 一样的价格
Yes. The price is all the same
# 只是按重量计价
The beef is sold by weight
# 一斤60元
60 yuan per Jin (0.5 kg)
# 我买这个是当公司下午茶
I'm buying this for my company's afternoon tea break
# 我买了差不多有2斤
I bought about 2 Jin (1 kg)
# 你们在这里吃吗
Are you eating here?
# 对啊
Yep
# 我不要牛杂里的牛肺
I don't want the lung
# 几个人吃啊
How many people are eating this?
# 2个 50块钱的差不多够吃吧
Two people. I think 50-yuan beef offal should be enough
# 哇 好大块的牛膀（胰腺）
Wow. Such a large piece of Niu Bang (beef pancreas)
# 豆腐要不要呢
Do you want some tofu?
# 少放一点就行
Just a few pieces, please
# 放辣椒吗
Chili pepper?
# 恩 放辣椒
Yes please
# 这是刚才一个湖南的小朋友
These snacks....
# 送给我们的零食
were given by a boy from Hunan Province
# 说我们一定要尝一尝 先收下了
He said we should definitely have a try. So I took them~
# 这个是我们买的50元的牛杂
This is the 50-yuan beef offal that we just bought
# 这里的牛杂是60元一斤
Here the beef offal is sold at 60 yuan per Jin (0.5 kg)
# 咱就是没要肺 其他的都要了
I ordered everything except beef lung
# 数一下大概有六七种牛杂
There are about 6 or 7 different types of beef offal
# 最后的时候 叔叔又放了辣酱
Before serving, the bro added some chili sauce
# 还有舀了一勺的卤汁
and a spoon of broth
# 这个带汤的牛杂吃起来应该不会很干
So the beef offal with some broth should not be very dry
# 不足之处 就是用了食品袋
But one problem is that he used a plastic bag
# 但是好在牛杂不是很烫（温热）
But it's OK because the beef offal is not very hot
# 所以说还可以接受
So this is acceptable
# 我们尝一尝这个吧
Let's taste it!
# 辣酱啊 馋人
Chili sauce. Yummy!
# 赶快多吃一点这个辣味
I should have more spicy sauce like this (before I leave)
# 因为走的时候就吃不到了
Because I won't be able to find it anywhere else
# 这块豆腐浸透了卤汁的味道
The tofu is filled with the taste of the broth
# 咬一口 汤直接就留在了嘴里
Take a bite, and the broth will stay in your mouth
# 吃一口 就感觉很入味
You can feel the perfect flavor penetration into the food as soon as you take a bite
# 这个大块的是牛膀 是牛胰腺
This large piece of meat is Niu Bang, aka beef pancreas
# 外形比较方正 吃起来很不怎么入味
It's cut into square dices. The flavor doesn't really penetrate inside
# 这边给的牛肠还是挺多的
He gave us a lot of beef intestines
# 蘸辣椒吃 这样不会很油腻
It doesn't feel greasy along with the chili sauce
# 几乎每一个部位 吃起来口感都不同
Each different part has a unique texture
# 有的容易吸收汤汁
Some absorb a lot of broth
# 有的口感比较筋道
Some are rather chewy
# 吃起来比较过瘾解馋
They'll relieve your craving for food
# 哇 这块肉好
Wow. A nice one
# 这是一个40年老摊
This is a 40-year-old shop
# 今天来这里买牛杂
Today when I was buying beef offal here
# 第一个是遇到某平台的粉丝朋友
I met some fans on another platform
# 第二个就是遇到了很可爱的湖南的小朋友
as well as a very cute boy from Hunan
# 真得是感觉这旅途很幸福
I really feel that this journey is worth it
# 别看这只是一个很小的摊
Though this is such a tiny shop
# 但是生意真的很好
It is popular indeed
# 咱们来的时候是需要排队的
We even needed to wait in line when we just arrived
# 很多顾客也是慕名来
Many customers are also attracted by its reputation
# 能看着大叔拿着一桶桶的牛杂往锅里倒
You can see that bro pouring beef offal from buckets into the pot
# 场面特别的壮观
which is an amazing scene
# 我要走了 拜拜
I'm going now. Bye-bye!